Academic Affairs and Provost, Office of Senior V.P. for; Records ua500
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Administrative Records, 1950-2021; 8; 21.03 cubic ft.
  - Intensive English Language Program, 1998; Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Survey, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Charter Schools Institute, 1998; 1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Academic Council, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - President's Report Submission, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Search File - Dean of the School of Social Welfare, 1998; 1999 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Small Business Development Center [3.5 in floppy], 1998; 1999 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Assistant Guidelines, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - CETL - Personnel, 1998; 2000 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - United States Department of Education - GEAR UP Program, 1998; 1999; 2000 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Mission Review, 1998-2000; Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Extended Learning (1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Extended Learning (2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Fort Orange Village, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - University Senate - Bills (1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - University Senate - Bills (2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Urban Education, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Department of Anthropology - Great Ideas Course, Presidential Scholars Course, 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Department of Chemistry, 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Department of Computer Science, 1998-2002; Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Department of Public Administration and Policy, 1998; 2001; 2002 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Rockefeller Colleges of Public Affairs and Policy, 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Mission Review, 1998; 2003; Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - School of Business, Dean - Richard Highfield, 1998; 1999; 2002; 2003 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - CETL - Personnel, 1998-2004 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - CETL, 1998; 2001; 2002; 2004; Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - United States Department of Education - GEAR UP Program, Proposal, 1999 April 29 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Rockefeller Colleges of Public Affairs and Policy - Strategic Plan, 1999 August 16 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Deans Council, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Department of Physics, Susanne Lee, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - NYSERNet National Science Foundation Proposal, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Search File - Dean of the School of Criminal Justice, 1999; 2000; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Search file - Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Search file - Deputy Director Center for Russia and the United States, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Surveys - National Study of Postsecondary Faculty, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - University Art Museum, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - University Art Museum - Strategic Planning Committee, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - United States Department of Education - GEAR UP Program [3.5 in Floppy], 1999 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Y2K Issues, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - College of Arts and Science, 1999; 2000 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cyprus Program, 1999; 2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Department of Pyschology, 1999; 2000 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - General Education, 1999; 2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - CETL - Strategic Planning, 1999; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Assistant Guidelines, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Tuition Opportunity Program, 1999; 2000 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Department of Biological Sciences, 1999; 2000; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Department of Physics, 1999; 2000; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Department of Psychology, 1999; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Financial Aid Reports, 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - NYSERNet, 1999; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy - Intergovernmental Solutions Project, 1999; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy - Reorganization, 1999; 2000; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - University Art Museum, 1999; 2000; 2001 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - NCAA Self-Study Steering Committee, 1999; 2000; 2001; Undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Department of Anthropology, 1999; 2000; 2001; 2002 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Department of Art, 1999; 2001; 2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - School of Education, 1999; 2000; 2001; 2002 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Cyprus, 1999-2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Department of Earth and Atmospheric Sciences, 1999-2003 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union Contract, 1999-2003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - United States Department of Education - GEAR UP Program, 1999; 2003 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Department of Africana Studies, 1999; 2000; 2001; 2002; 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Audit Report - Financial Disclosure Reporting For Academic Employees, 2000 November (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cyprus Ambassador, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - General Education, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Mission Review Funding, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy - Restructuring, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - CETL - Smart Classroom Initiative (Folder 1), 2000; 2001 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - CETL - Smart Classroom Initiative (Folder 2), 2000; 2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - CETL - Smart Classroom Initiative (Folder 3), 2000; 2001 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Program Review Committee (1 of 2), 2000; 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Program Review Committee (2 of 2), 2000; 2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Research Foundation Memoranda - Graduate Assistantships, 2000; 2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Surveys, 2000; 2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Surveys - Student Opinion Survey, 2000; 2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Assistant Task Force, 2000; 2001; 2002 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Institutional Research, 2000; 2001; 2002 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Graduate Assistantship and fellowship - Tuition Scholarship Allocation, 2000; 2001; 2002; Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Graduate Assistantship and fellowship - Tuition Scholarship Allocation, 2000; 2001; 2002; Undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Graduate Assistantship and fellowship - Tuition Scholarship Allocation, 2000; 2001; 2002; Undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Mission Review Stipend Committee, 2000; 2001; 2002 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - School of Criminal Justice, 2000; 2001; 2002 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - School of Criminal Justice, Dean - James Acker, 2000; 2001; 2002 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Administrative Graduate Assistantship Awards, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Cyprus Program, 2000; 2001; 2002; 2003 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Certification, 2000; 2001; 2002; 2003; Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Mission Review Funding, 2000-2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - CETL - Hesburg Award, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Cyprus - Visit from Nicos Rolandis, Minister of Commerce, Industry, and Toursim, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Department of Communication, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - General Education, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - GA Residency Requirements, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - General Human Resources Information, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Assistant News, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Assistant and Teaching Assistant funding and Appointment Proccess, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Institutional Research - Graduate Program GRE and GPA quality profiles, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Master Plan (2000-2004), 2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Mission Review Survey, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Office of the Vice President for Research - Institute for Health and the Environment, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - New York State Biodiversity Institute, 2001; Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - School of Education - Summer in the City Program, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Alliance for Inclusive Graduate Education and the Professoriate, 2001; 2002 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 2001; 2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Cyprus Program, 2001; 2002 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Deans Council, 2001; 2002 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Graduate Assistant Guidelines, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Graduate Assistant Task Force, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Graduate Policy Changes, 2001; 2002 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Office of the Vice President for Research, 2001; 2002 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Outcomes Assessment, 2001; 2002 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy - NASPAA, 2001; 2002 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - World Trade Center Tragedy: Responses from Doctor Hitchcock, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - University Art Museum, 2001; 2002; Undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Financial Aid Issues, 2002 March 27 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Financial Planning, 2002 March (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, Space Planning, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - College Scholars Program, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Deans' Retreat, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - I-20 Certification Policy, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Middle States - Substantive Change Proposal, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Surveys - Survey of Chief Academic Officers, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Targeted/Minority Issues, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - University Senate - Bills, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - College of Arts and Sciences, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - Information Technology, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - Rockefeller College for Public Affairs and Policy, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - School of Business, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - School of Criminal Justice, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - School of Education, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - School of Information Science and Policy, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - School of Nanosciences and Materials, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Budget, Reconciliation - School of Public Health, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Budget, Reduction - College of Arts and Sciences, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Budget, Reduction - Office of International Education, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Budget, Reduction - Office of Undergraduate Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Budget, Reduction - Provost's Office and Academic Support Units, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Budget, Reduction - School of Education, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Budget, Reduction - University Art Museum, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Budget, Submission - CETL, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Budget, Submission - College of Arts and Sciences, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Budget, Submission - Enrollment Management, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Budget, Submission - New York State Writers Institute, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Budget, Submission - Office of the Registrar, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Budget, Submission - Project Renaissance, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Budget, Submission - Rockefeller College for Public Affairs and Policy, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Budget, Submission - School of Business, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Budget, Submission - School of Criminal Justice, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Budget, Submission - School of Education, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Budget, Submission - School of Information Science and Policy, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Budget, Submission - School of Nanoscience and Materials, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Budget, Submission - School of Public Health, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Deans Council Meetings, 2002; 2003 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Studies Correspondence and Meeting Notes, 2002; 2003 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Task Force on Faculty Development, 2002; 2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - CETL - Innovation Fund for Teaching, 2003; Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Surveys - Student Opinion Survey, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - School of Education, Dean - Susan Phillips, 2003; 2004; 2005 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - School of Business, Dean - Paul Leonard, 2004; 2005 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - College of Arts and Science Dean - Joan Wick Pelletier, 2004; 2005; Undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy, Dean - Frank Thompson, 2004; 2005; Undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - School of Social Welfare - Katherine Briar-Lawson, 2004; Undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - School of Criminal Justice, Dean - Julie Horney, ca. 2004 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Space Planning, 1967; 1968; 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Budget (1968-69), 1967; 1969; Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Requested New Positions, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Budget (1969-70), 1968; Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - State Support of Organized Research in the State Universiy of New York, A Proposed Statement, 1969 September 12 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Budget (1970-71), 1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Budget (1970-71, Folder 1), 1969; Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Budget (1970-71, Folder 2), 1969; Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Budget (1970-71, Folder 3), 1969; Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Budget and Planning, 1969; 1970; Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - New York State Writers Institute, 2001; 2002; 2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 8-Inch Floppies, 1982-1983; 1985; 1987; Undated (Box 24)
  - Academic Affairs Budget Planning Timeline, 2020-2021
  - Academic Affairs Proposed Budget Metrics, 2021 January 20
    - Academic Affairs Proposed Budget Metrics, 2021 January 20
    - Academic Affairs Proposed Budget Metrics, 2021 January 20
  - UAlbany Department Profiles, 2020 November 20
  - United University Professions Budget Letter, 2021 January 2
  - Academic Affairs Budget Planning Town Hall, 2021 January 27
- Deactivated and Discontinued Programs, 2010-2018
  This series is not comphrensive and may not include every program discontinued during this time period.
  - SUNY Albany Discontinuance M.S. Accounting Information Systems, 2018-11-13
  - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Multiple Academic Programs after the Inventory of Registered Programs (IRP), 2018
    - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Multiple Academic Programs after the Inventory of Registered Programs (IRP), 2018
    - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Multiple Academic Programs after the Inventory of Registered Programs (IRP), 2018
    - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Multiple Academic Programs after the Inventory of Registered Programs (IRP), 2018
    - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Multiple Academic Programs after the Inventory of Registered Programs (IRP), 2018
    - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Multiple Academic Programs after the Inventory of Registered Programs (IRP), 2018
    - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Multiple Academic Programs after the Inventory of Registered Programs (IRP), 2018
  - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of the B.S. and M.S. programs in Nanoscale Engineering, 2014-2017
  - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Public Affairs and Policy Programs, 2010
  - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Puerto Rican Studies programs, 2015-2016
  - SUNY Albany Discontinuance in Russian Graduate Studies, 2010
  - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security and Cybersecurity, B.S., 2023
  - SUNY Albany Discontinuance of Accounting/Law, B.S., J.D., 2023